There is an emotion we call "fear."
It is a natural emotion inherent in all animals.
What exactly causes fear to occur?
There is the fear caused by primal instincts,
and the fear born of logical thought...
The fear when you encounter someone stronger than yourself
whom you have no way of defeating...
Or perhaps the fear of encountering something unknown.
To think even something as simple as the unknown can evoke fear.
When faced with fear, you have a number of choices.
You might struggle, resist, flee,
accept your fate, or something else entirely.
But upon meeting Lord Dio, a new reaction arises...
Joy!
How does a person react to feeling joy while in fear?
Your follower is currently on the plane with Joestar and the others.
They will not reach their destination safely.
R-Rhinoceros beetle?
No...
A stag beetle!
Abdul, is it a Stand?
Could we already be encountering another Stand user?
Quite possibly.
It could be a bug-shaped Stand.
It hid in the shadow of the seats...
W-Where is it?
Jojo! It's right next to you!
Soshite tsudoishi stardust
As it is told, the gathering Stardust
Hyakunen me no mezameni yobarete
Will awaken a century-old destiny
Otoko tachi wa mukau
A group of men must depart
Toki no suna wo koeru journey
On a journey through the sands of time
Kusari no you tsuranaru
Their karma links them together
Karamiau karuma
Like a chain
Hikari de tatsu sadame
A fate that becomes obscured by the light
Stand Up Stand Up Stand Up uchi komu no wa
Stand up, stand up, stand up, shoot straight ahead
All Right Now All Right Now All Right Now hokori no bullet
All right now, all right now, all right now, a bullet of pride
Break You Down Break You Down Break You Down kobushi hanatsu
Break you down, break you down, break you down, let loose your fists
Seinaru Vision Stand Proud!
This sacred vision will Stand Proud!
Episode 4: Tower of Gray
I-It's huge! It must be a Stand.
That bug has to be a Stand!
It's fucking gross.
Anyway, I'll deal with it.
B-Be careful...
I have heard of a user with a bug Stand who enjoys ripping the tongue out of its victims.
Star Platinum!
I-It dodged!
U-Unbelievable!
Star Platinum has enough speed and precision to grasp a bullet, yet it is still faster!
It must be a Stand. That bug has to be a Stand!
Where did it go? Where is it hiding?!
And where is the person controlling it?!
I-It's attacking!
Shit!
Jotaro!
Jojo!
It's good that he could stop the needle with his mouth, but...
Since it tried to bite off the tongue of Jotaro's Stand...
...it must be him!
The Tower Tarot card...
His Stand symbolizes destruction,
calamity, and the interruption of journeys...
Tower of Gray!
Tower of Gray is a malicious Stand who commits mass murder by framing his kills as accidents.
The airplane crash responsible for 300 deaths last year in England is thought to be his doing.
They were only rumors, but he really is working for Dio!
Ora!
Ora Ora Ora Ora!
I-It dodged!
It evaded blows from not only one fist, but both simultaneously!
I-It's so fast...
Even if you shot ten guns simultaneously from
one centimeter away, they would never be able to touch my Stand!
Not that a bullet would kill my Stand, anyway.
He has to be nearby!
Who is it?
Where's the person controlling the Stand?
Which one of the passengers is he?
If we can just track him down...
It disappeared again.
It moved over there!
What is it doing?
I-Impossible!
Bingo!
I got their tongues!
And now...
Massacre!
In other words, a slaughter!
I-It actually did it...
I will burn it asunder!
Magician's Red!
Wait! Don't do it, Abdul!
It's so noisy...
What's with the ruckus?
Look out!
Guess I'll use the toilet.
What... is this?
M... a...
I-Is it blood?! Blood!
Quiet!
We need to have this taken care of
before the other passengers panic.
But, Mr. Abdul...
Your Magician's Red would be felt by everyone and cause the plane to explode.
Jojo, if you were to punch a hole in the fuselage,
it would be a disaster.
My Stand is the best choice here.
Hierophant Green is inconspicuous and best suited for defeating it.
Kakyoin Noriaki, eh?
I've heard all about you from Lord Dio.
Don't bother.
If you know your Stand is no match for mine,
then don't even challenge me.
You cannot catch me at your speed!
Is that so?
Emerald Splash!
It seems like you're dumb enough to think you'll hit me with enough shots, but none of them are connecting!
Not good. It is dodging far too fast!
K-Kakyoin!
My speed is on an entirely different level!
You'll never get a bingo at that speed.
Now then, Kakyoin...
With my next attack, I'll stab your Stand's tongue with my Tower Needle, and rip it out!
Emerald Splash!
Don't you get it?
N-Not good! It dodged Emerald Splash again!
After tearing its tongue out, your Stand will shudder...
...in utter pain!
What? Shuddering when its tongue is torn out?
My Hierophant Green?
What?!
It will shudder all right...
...with pleasure!
My Hierophant's tendrils had already slipped beneath the seats.
Didn't you realize I was trapping you there with Emerald Splash?
So that old man was the user?
A disgusting Stand for a disgusting user.
He doesn't appear to have Dio's flesh bud in his forehead.
Tower of Gray is an evil Stand that was infamous for murdering tourists,
making it appear to be an accident in return for pay.
Dio was able to manipulate him since he is easily bought and blinded by greed.
That's weird...
It could be my imagination, but it feels like we're flying crooked.
It is crooked.
I-It can't be!
Sir, where are you going?
The cockpit is up ahead, no passengers allowed.
I know that!
S-Sir!
Wow! He's gorgeous.
Move, woman.
What a shock!
Whoa, there.
Pardon me.
Treating a woman like that is inexcusable...
...but this is an emergency.
Please forgive him.
Okay...
This is awful!
We've been had!
Their tongues were ripped out.
That fucking stag beetle!
He already killed the pilots?
We're descending.
The autopilot's damaged, as well.
We're gonna crash!
What?
I control the Tower card, the symbol of
calamity and the interruption of journeys.
You will never reach Lord Dio!
Even if you survive the crash,
you're 10,000 kilometers away from Egypt!
Those who swore loyalty to Lord Dio
will hunt you every hour of every day!
There are Stands in this world beyond your wildest imaginations!
Lord Dio is the master of Stands!
Lord Dio has the power to reign over all of them!
You'll never reach him!
You bastards will never reach Egypt!
You're well trained.
If you had screamed, it would have pissed me off.
I have a request.
Gramps here is gonna make an emergency landing on the water.
Get the passengers in life jackets and buckle them in.
G-Got it!
Gramps...
I have experience flying propeller planes, but...
Propeller?
But Jotaro... this would be my third time crashing a plane.
Have you ever heard of someone being in three plane crashes?
Never again...
Never again am I flying with you.
To
Towe
Tower
Tower o
Tower of
Tower of Gr
Tower of Gra
Gr
Tower of Gray
Gra
Gray
Gray F
Power: E
Speed: A
Range: A
Durability: C
Precision: E
Growth Potential: E
Gray Fl
Gray Fly
Their plane landed 35 kilometers off the coast of Hong Kong.
Jotaro and company had no choice but to head to Hong Kong.
Today, a jumbo jet made an emergency landing
35 kilometers south of Hong Kong, near Lamma Island.
Rescue efforts are underway...
Hong Kong!
Hong Kong Island! Kowloon! The New Territories!
With more than 235 islands in the area...
— Hong Kong —
...the sight of the bay at night is known as the "Million Dollar View."
Right. That's fine.
Make sure only the crew and our group are on board.
Right. We don't want any more victims.
Also...
Hey, big guy!
Are you fellas tourists?
Wanna try my rice porridge?
Since you're in Hong Kong,
you just have to try dim sum or rice porridge!
We have hot cola, too.
Rice porridge, eh? Not bad.
Did you know, Jojo?
Unlike Japan, rice porridge is a staple food here.
I'll have the regional style, with pork and a century egg.
Sure thing!
And I will have...
Hey!
Why are you guys getting food already?
We're gonna pay a visit to my friend's shop.
You sure look dandy! Would you like Hong Kong's own hot cola?
Hot?!
Everyone knows you only serve cola cold!
Gramps, who was that on the phone?
Oh, I'll explain everything once we get there.
We need to work out a plan that'll
get us to Egypt as quickly and safely as possible.
A plan?
Mr. Joestar, we cannot allow any more innocent people to be hurt.
Although the quickest route would be by plane...
You got it.
Flying to Egypt is simply no longer a possibility.
If we encounter another Stand user like on the last flight,
we would be putting even more innocent people in harm's way.
We'll have to reach Egypt by either land or sea.
However, if we fail to find Dio within fifty days...
If we had chosen another plane, we'd probably be in Cairo by now.
Maybe so...
...but now isn't the time to get upset over it.
One hundred years ago, Jules Verne wrote a story in which a man traveled around the world, a total of forty thousand kilometers, in eighty days.
That was in the age of trains and steamboats.
Even without a plane, we can definitely travel
the ten thousand kilometers to Egypt in fifty days.
As for the route...
We'll head to Cairo by sea.
We'll charter a suitably-sized boat, go around
the Malay peninsula, and cross the Indian Ocean.
It will be the Silk Road of the sea.
I also believe this is best.
If we travel by land, the borders will be a nuisance,
and we would be crossing both the desert and the Himalayas.
Any trouble will cost us valuable time.
It is too dangerous.
I've never been to any of the places along either route, so I have no preference.
I'll leave it up to you two.
I agree.
Then it's decided.
The greatest danger will be the Stand users that Dio sends after us.
We'll have to do our best to get to Egypt without being spotted.
This is a sign to let them know we want more tea.
If you do this in Hong Kong, they'll bring you more.
Also, when they pour tea into your cup...
...this means "thank you."
Excuse me, do you have a moment?
I'm a tourist from France, you see.
I'm having a hard time understanding the menu.
Could ya help a guy out?
Talk about annoying. Fuck off.
Come on, Jotaro... It's fine.
I've been to Hong Kong countless times.
I should be able to read the menu.
Why don't you join us?
So, what did you want to order?
Food with shrimp, duck, shark fin and mushrooms?
We'll have this, this, this...
And this, too.
Oh, and this.
This is beef, fish, clams, and frog, but...
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Roasted Frog
Rice Porridge
Clam Dish
Stewed Fish
Indeed. This is all wrong...
This figures.
Well, no worries!
It's on me!
It doesn't matter what you order, it's all good!
Now, everyone, let's eat!
Wow, this is...
Well? It's pretty good, huh?
Well, they certainly took long enough making it.
Look, these carrots...
They're shaped like stars.
It reminds me of something...
That's right.
Someone I know has a mark
that looks exactly like this on their neck...
You...
Are you another...
Mr. Joestar, look out!
It's a Stand!
Magician's Red!
What?!
Another Stand user!
H-His sword is so fast...
My Stand represents the Chariot card!
Silver Chariot!
Mohammed Abdul, it appears that you wish to die first.
I've made a fire clock on that table!
I'll kill you before the clock strikes twelve!
All the old paintings on the tomb
They do the sand dance, don'tcha know?
If they move too quick
They're falling down like a domino
All the bazaar men by the Nile
They got the money on a bet
Gold crocodiles
They snap their teeth on your cigarette
Foreign types with their hookah pipes say
Walk like an Egyptian
The blonde waitresses take their trays
They spin around and they cross the floor
They got the moves
You drop your drink then they bring you more
All the school kids so sick of books
They like the punk and the metal band
When the buzzer rings
They're walking like an Egyptian
All the kids in the marketplace say
Walk like an Egyptian
Next Episode
Would you like to be my friend?
I can sense you're distressed.
Stay by my side, and it will disappear from your heart.
Your left hand wouldn't happen to be the same as your right, would it?
If you wanted to fight a fortune teller with predictions...
Episode 5
Silver Chariot